(gentle wistful music)
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Can't hold it back anymore ♪
♪ Turn my back and slam the door ♪
♪ The snow glows white
on the mountain tonight ♪
♪ Not a footprint to be seen ♪
♪ A kingdom of isolation ♪
♪ And it looks like I'm the queen ♪
♪ The wind is howling like
this swirling storm inside ♪
♪ Couldn't keep it in,
heaven knows I tried ♪
♪ Don't let them in, don't let them see ♪
♪ Be the good girl you always have to be ♪
♪ Conceal, don't feel,
don't let them know ♪
♪ Well, now they know ♪
(spirited upbeat music)
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Can't hold it back anymore ♪
♪ Turn my back and slam the door ♪
♪ And here I stand ♪
♪ And here I'll stay ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ The cold never bothered me anyway ♪
♪ It's funny how some distance ♪
♪ Makes everything seem small ♪
♪ And the fears that once controlled me ♪
♪ Can't get to me at all ♪
♪ Up here in the cold, thin air ♪
♪ I finally can breathe ♪
♪ I know I left a life behind ♪
♪ But I'm to relieved to grieve ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Can't hold it back anymore ♪
♪ Turn my back and slam the door ♪
♪ And here I stand ♪
♪ And here I'll stay ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ The cold never bothered me anyway ♪
♪ Standing, frozen ♪
♪ In the life I've chosen ♪
♪ You won't find me ♪
♪ The past is so behind me ♪
♪ Buried in the snow ♪
(gentle wistful music)
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Can't hold it back anymore ♪
(spirited upbeat music)
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Turn my back and slam the door ♪
♪ And here I stand ♪
♪ And here I'll stay ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ The cold never bothered me anyway ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Yeah, oh ♪
♪ Na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ You would die ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
(spirited upbeat music swells)